I am Kim Jae-hoon,
Proxy Driver
Once, I lived as a respected human being
with a full-time job.
But now, I am nothing more than a "proxy"
A nameless driver
who jumps at every command
takes all the abuse,
and has to cater to every drunken whim.
Student loans are still pending,
and I couldn't even pay this month's rent
Everyone has the right to live with dignity.
But inside this car,
that belief is trampled every single moment.
Jae-hoon, you're doing okay, right? Don't push yourself too hard. I'm doing fine, so just focus on staying healthy
"Fine," my foot...
You can't even afford the doctor
if I don't send you money.
Driver App
You bitch... you fucking bitch...
how could you do this to me?
Get the hell out, you bitch!
Hello. Did you call for a driver?
"Proxy Driver"
(Episode 1)
Sir, we have arrived.
I said, we've arrived, sir.
What the hell?
Look at this piece of shit.
Hello? Is this the police station?
I caught a thief here.
Sir? Oh, I am so sorry.
I lost my mind for a second.
Please forgive me.
Just this once.
I'll never do it again
I'll do anything you tell me to.
Really?
Suck it.
...What?
I said, suck it.
That's... I can't...
Look at this prick.
Hello?
ok. I'll do it.
Should've done that from the start
You better do a good job
if you don't want to rot in jail.
Is it... is it over now? Can I go?
Scumbag.